Guide to the Melville Cane Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Cataloged Correspondence
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Stanford University, 13 Nov 1942, (2 pages t.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Stanford University, 14 May 1943, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Stanford University, 30 Nov 1943, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Stanford University, 6 March 1944, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 29 Jan 1945, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 9 Feb 1945, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Hanover, NH, 18 March 1945, (2 pages t.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Hanover, NH, 11 Nov 1945, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Hanover, NH, 11 Jan 1946, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Hanover, NH, 27 Feb 1946, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Hanover, NH, 30 Dec 1946, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Hanover, NH, 19 Jan 1947, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Hanover, NH, 12 April 1947, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 3 June 1947, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Hanover, NH, 3 Oct 1947, (2 pages t.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 13 July 1950, (3 pages t.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, New York, 28 Nov 1950, (1 page p.c.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 2 Sept 1950, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, New York, 25 Feb 1951, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 15 Sept 1951, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 7 Oct 1951, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, New York, 2 April 1952, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 19 April 1952, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, n.p., 21 April 1952, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 8 Sept 1952, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, n.p., 18 Sept 1952, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 19 Oct 1952, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Philadelphia, 4 Dec 1952, (2 pages t.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 22 Dec 1952, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 27 Dec 1952, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Philadelphia, 19 Jan 1953, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Paris, 8 June 1953, (1 page p.c.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Oxford, England, 18 Aug 1953, (1 page p.c.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Philadelphia, 11 Dec 1953, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Philadelphia, 3 Oct 1954, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Philadelphia, 10 Oct 1954, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 5 Jan 1955, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Philadelphia, 13 Jan 1955, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Philadelphia, 25 Jan 1955, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Philadelphia, 21 Oct 1955, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Philadelphia, 29 Oct 1955, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 28 Feb 1956, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 11 May 1956, (1 page p.c.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 4 Feb 1957, (4 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, On board ship, 31 March 1957, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Paris, 22 April 1957, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Ledbury, England, 5 July 1957, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 11 Aug 1957, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 4 Oct 1957, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 31 Oct 1957, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 8 Dec 1957, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 20 Dec 1958, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 1 Feb 1958, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 18 Sept 1958, (1 page p.c.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 12 Oct 1958, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 19 Oct 1958, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 25 Jan 1959, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 10 April 1959, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, n.p., 27 June 1959, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 25 Oct 1959, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 4 Dec 1959, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 18 Dec 1959, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 7 Jan 1960, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 10 Feb 1960, (3 pages t.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 14 Feb 1960, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 19 March 1960, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, n.p., 17 Oct 1963, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Philadelphia, 4 Nov 1960, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 3 Feb 1961, (2 pages t.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, London, 2 July 1961, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 10 Feb 1963, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 3 March 1963, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 19 March 1963, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 25 March 1963, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 2 April 1963, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 12 April 1963, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Middletown, CT, 25 Nov 1963, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Middletown, CT, 15 Dec 1963, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Middletown, CT, 5 Jan 1964, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Middletown, CT, 11 Jan 1964, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Middletown, CT, 21 Jan 1964, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 8 March 1964, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, n.p., 22 March 1964, (1 page a.l.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 16 June 1964, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 17 Aug 1964, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 14 Nov 1964, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 13 Dec 1964, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 17 Jan 1965, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 10 Feb 1965, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 26 Feb 1965, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 26 March 1965, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Edinburgh, Scotland, 8 July 1965, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Boston, 13 Nov 1965, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 2 Feb 1966, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 24 Feb 1966, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 10 April 1966, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Little Troutbeck, NY, 8 July 1966, (1 page a.l.s. (s. The Sage of Leedsville)) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 28 Aug 1966, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 5 Sept 1966, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 9 Oct 1966, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 7 Dec 1966, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 23 Dec 1966, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 21 Jan 1967, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 30 Jan 1967, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 20 Feb 1967, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 12 April 1967, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Rome, 29 May 1967, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, London, 27 June 1967, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 2 Oct 1967, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 19 Oct 1967, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 4 Nov 1967, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 15 Dec 1967, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 18 Feb 1968, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 1 April 1968, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 14 June 1968, (1 page p.c.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 24 Oct 1968, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 9 Nov 1968, (3 pages t.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 7 Dec 1968, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 1 Jan 1969, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 30 Jan 1969, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, [Cambridge, MA], 10 March 1969, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 21 March 1969, (1 a.p.c.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 12 April 1969, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 18 Oct 1969, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 20 Dec 1969, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 1 Feb 1970, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, [18 Feb 1970], (1 p.c.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 25 Feb 1970, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, [Cambridge, MA], 13 April 1970, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 18 Aug 1970, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, n.p., 25 Sept [1970], (1 page a.l.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 21 Oct 1970, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 29 Nov 1970, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 17 Dec 1970, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 3)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 6 Feb 1971, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 30 March 1971, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 29 Oct 1971, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 7 Nov 1971, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 16 Nov 1971, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 26 Nov 1971, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 20 Dec 1971, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
    [With enclosure]
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Charlottesville, VA, 21 Feb 1972, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Charlottesville, VA, 27 March 1972, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 16 April 1972, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 10 May 1972, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 16 May 1972, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 29 May 1972, (2 pages t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 31 May 1972, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 15 July 1972, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 2 Sept 1972, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 24 Sept 1972, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 3 Nov 1972, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 19 Dec 1972, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 10 Jan 1973, (2 pages t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 14 March 1973, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 6 April 1973, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 21 May 1973, (2 pages t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 4 June 1973, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 14 July 1973, (4 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 23 July 1973, (1 a.p.c.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 23 Sept 1973, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 9 Dec 1973, (2 pages t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 24 Jan 1974, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 9 July 1974, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 28 July 1974, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 10 Sept 1974, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 22 Nov 1974, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis and Sophia To Melville Cane, [Amenia, NY,], ca. Dec [1974], (1 page a.l.s. (on Christmas card)) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 24 Jan 1975, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 12 June 1975, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 26 July 1975, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 30 Sept 1975, (2 pages t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 26 Jan 1976, (2 pages t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 12 Feb 1976, (2 pages a.l.s. (with envelope)) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 5 March 1976, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 11 April 1976, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 30 Sept 1976, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 19 Oct 1976, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis and Sophia To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 18 Dec 1976, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis and Sophia To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 25 Dec 1976, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 10 March 1977, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 11 April 1977, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis and Sophia To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 11 Sept 1977, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 25 Dec 1977, (2 pages t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 16 March 1978, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Lewis and Sophia To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 11 April 1978, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Sophia (Mrs. Lewis) To Melville Cane, n.p., n.d., (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Sophia (Mrs. Lewis) To Melville Cane, Hanover, NH, 11 March 1948, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Sophia (Mrs. Lewis) To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 24 Dec 1962, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Sophia (Mrs. Lewis) To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 16 March 1964, (2 pages t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Sophia (Mrs. Lewis) To Melville Cane, n.p., Dec 1965, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Sophia (Mrs. Lewis) To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 20 Feb 1966, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Sophia (Mrs. Lewis) To Melville Cane, [Cambridge, MA], [Dec 1966], (2 pages a.l.s. (on Christmas card)) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Sophia (Mrs. Lewis) To Melville Cane, n.p., 9 Dec 1966, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Sophia (Mrs. Lewis) To Melville Cane, n.p., 13 July 1968, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Sophia (Mrs. Lewis) To Melville Cane, Cambridge, MA, 25 Dec 1968, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Mumford, Sophia (Mrs. Lewis) To Melville Cane, Amenia, NY, 20 Oct 1975, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, New York, 20 March 1932, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, New York, 31 May 1932, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, New York, 8 Aug 1933, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, New York, 28 Nov 1934, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, New York, 12 April 1935, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, Scarsdale, NY, 18 Sept 1938, (1 p.c.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, Kansas City, MO, [June 1948], (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, New York, 23 June 1948, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, New York, 2 Dec 1948, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, New York, 6 Feb 1949, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, New York, 11 April 1949, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, New York, 1 May 1949, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, New York, 25 Jan 1950, (2 pages t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, New York, 17 March 1950, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, New York, 19 Sept 1950, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, New York, 15 Oct 1950, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, Staten Island, 8 July 1956, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, New York, 12 March 1957, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, Madison, NJ, 14 July 1962, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, New York, 9 Sept 1964, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, n.p., [Nov 1964], (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 4)
    [Written on related letter]
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, New York, 9 May 1966, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, New York, 18 Sept 1966, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, Davis, CA, 27 Oct 1966, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, Davis, CA, 15 Nov 1966, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, Palm Springs, CA, 27 Dec 1966, (1 p.c.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, Davis, CA, 8 Feb 1967, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, Davis, CA, 16 April 1967, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, Davis, CA, 9 June 1967, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, Middletown, CT, 15 Dec 1967, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, Middletown, CT, 5 Feb 1968, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Munson, Gorham To Melville Cane, Middletown, CT, 24 July 1968, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 4)
  - Nash, Ogden To Melville Cane, New York, 13 Jan 1931, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - Nash, Ogden To Melville Cane, North Hampton, NH, 24 July 1967, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - Nicholson, Meredith To Melville Cane, Indianapolis, 12 Jan 1921, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - Nicholl, Louise Townsend To Melville Cane, New York, 7 June 1960, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - Nock, Albert Jay To Melville Cane, New York, 3-9 Aug 1922, (3 t.l.s.) (Box 5)
    [With copy of a reply]
  - O'Neill, Carlotta Monterey (Mrs. Eugene) To Melville Cane, Danville, CA, 28 July 1938, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - O'Neill, Carlotta Monterey (Mrs. Eugene) To Melville Cane, n.p., 11 July 1939, (1 page p.c.s.) (Box 5)
  - O'Neill, Carlotta Monterey (Mrs. Eugene) To Melville Cane, Danville, CA, 23 Nov 1943, (4 pages a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - O'Neill, Carlotta Monterey (Mrs. Eugene) To Melville Cane, n.p., 5 April 1945, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - O'Neill, Carlotta Monterey (Mrs. Eugene) To Melville Cane, [New York?], 12 Oct 1946, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - O'Neill, Carlotta Monterey (Mrs. Eugene) To Melville Cane, New York, 31 March 1947, (3 pages a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - O'Neill, Carlotta Monterey (Mrs. Eugene) To Melville Cane, n.p., n.d. & 1947, (2 Christmas cards, s.) (Box 5)
  - O'Neill, Carlotta Monterey (Mrs. Eugene) To Melville Cane, n.p., 16 Dec 1952, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - O'Neill, Carlotta Monterey (Mrs. Eugene) To Melville Cane, n.p., 18 Feb 1953, (4 pages a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - O'Neill, Carlotta Monterey (Mrs. Eugene) To Melville Cane, Boston, 27 Feb 1953, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - O'Neill, Carlotta Monterey (Mrs. Eugene) To Melville Cane, Boston, 30 Dec 1953, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - O'Neill, Eugene To [Melville Cane], n.p., n.d., (2 Christmas cards, s. by O'Neill and Mrs. O'Neill) (Box 5)
  - O'Neill, Eugene To Melville Cane, Seattle, 17 Nov 1936, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - O'Neill, Eugene To Melville Cane, [Boston], 9 April 1948, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - O'Neill, Eugene To Melville Cane, Boston, 6 June 1948, (3 pages ms.l.s. (in hand of Mrs. O'Neill)) (Box 5)
    [In reply to: [Cane, Melville]. To Mrs. Eugene O'Neill, 3 June 1948.]
  - Orage, Alfred Richard To Melville Cane, London, n.d., (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - Orage, Alfred Richard To Melville Cane, New York, 10 May 1928, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - Orage, Alfred Richard To Melville Cane, New York, 16 Jan 1929, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - Orage, Alfred Richard To Melville Cane, New York, [Jan 1930], (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - Orage, Alfred Richard To Melville Cane, New York, 3 Feb 1930, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - Orage, Alfred Richard To Melville Cane, [London?], 4 Sept 1930, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - Orage, Alfred Richard To Melville Cane, London, 6 Feb 1932, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - Orage, Alfred Richard To Melville Cane, London, [ca. March 1932], (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - Orage, Alfred Richard To Melville Cane, London, 21 March 1932, (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - Orage, Alfred Richard To Melville Cane, London, 17 June 1932, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - Orage, Alfred Richard To Melville Cane, London, 18 July 1933, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - Orage, Alfred Richard To Melville Cane, London, 5 Jan 1934, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - Orage, Alfred Richard To Melville Cane, London, 13 April 1934, (2 pages a.l.s.) (Box 5)
  - Pearson, Norman Holmes To Melville Cane, New Haven, CT, n.d., (1 page a.l.s.) (Box 5)
    [With related items]